thoughtequity.com 2016-05-05

# Privacy Policy - Wazee Digital (Thought Equity)

**Privacy Policy**

**Last Updated: April 11, 2012**

**Our Commitment to Privacy**

Wazee Digital, Inc. (“ **Wazee Digital** ”) respects your right to privacy and utilizes the following practices (“ **Privacy Policy** ”) in regards to any information we are provided about users of the Wazee Digital Website located at [www.wazeedigital.com](http://www.wazeedigital.com/) (the “ **Website** ”). Please review this Privacy Policy prior to using the Wazee Digital Website since it may be changed periodically without notice to you. In addition, our [online terms of use](http://commerce.wazeedigital.com/license/home/terms_of_use.do) (” **Terms of Use** “) describe the obligations and restrictions you agree to in exchange for being allowed to use our Website. Together, our Privacy Policy and Terms of Use form a legally binding contract between you and us. 

In order to fulfill licensing transactions or provide service to you as a customer of Wazee Digital, we may require you to provide certain information to us. Common items may include, but are not limited to, your name, address, email address, phone number and credit card information. 

By providing this information to Wazee Digital, you are agreeing to allow us to utilize this information to complete all transactions you request through the Website and to disclose that information and details of all such transactions to Wazee Digital’s various worldwide offices, subsidiaries, affiliates and any necessary payment processors. Because of the nature of the Internet, such data may pass through any country. 

Wazee Digital may share your personal information with third party service providers who perform services on behalf of Wazee Digital. For example, payment processing vendors, fulfillment and shipment vendors and direct marketing vendors. Those service providers will be permitted to obtain only the personal information they need to provide the designated service. They are required to maintain the confidentiality of the information and are prohibited from using it for any purpose outside the scope of their services. 

Except as otherwise described in this Privacy Policy, Wazee Digital does not disclose or release your personal information to third parties; provided that, to the extent permitted by law, Wazee Digital may use or disclose personal information: (a) for compliance purposes, such as immigration and customs control, security, and legal support; (b) in connection with legal requests from (i) government authorities or (ii) third parties pursuant to a subpoena or other legal process; (c) to perform payment verifications, debt reporting or collection, or to otherwise protect the rights or property of Wazee Digital, its employees, customers, or end users; or (d) if we sell or otherwise transfer substantially all of our assets related to any website that we own or operate and any product or service that we offer, in which event, we will require such third party to honor our current Privacy Policy, until the third party provides you with notice of changes to the Privacy Policy and permits you to exercise any rights you may have under applicable law to limit disclosures of information about you. 

**Notifications**

From time to time we may notify you of special promotions, new products or services, or other information that may interest you. We may do so using either the email or the mailing addresses you provided on the registration or billing information screens or to a Wazee Digital representative. Should you not wish to receive this type of information, you shall have the ability to opt out of such communications at any time by clicking on the unsubscribe option available in each email communication. Unless otherwise described in this Privacy Policy, Wazee Digital does not sell or share e-mail addresses with third parties for their promotional or commercial purposes. We may use your e-mail address to contact you with respect to an order or inquiry you make on the Website. If we change our Privacy Policy, we will post those changes on our Website to keep you aware of what information we collect, how we use it and under what circumstances we may disclose it. 

If at any time you believe that Wazee Digital has not followed the above policy, or if you would like your information to be removed from our system, please e-mail us at [legal@wazeedigital.com](mailto:legal@wazeedigital.com). 

**Automatically Collected Information and Use**

When you access and use the Wazee Digital Website, we automatically collect some information, through certain web technologies such as “cookies,” regarding your computer usage and store it in log files. This information includes the internet protocol (IP) address, browser type, internet service provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, operating system, date/time stamp, and click stream data. 

We use this unidentifiable information to analyze trends, to administer the Website, to track users’ movements around the Website and to gather demographic information about our user base as a whole. 

Wazee Digital also utilizes third party vendors, including Google, to show Wazee Digital advertisements on the Internet. 

Additionally, we do collect personally identifiable information such as IP addresses for analytical purposes. 

**Security Features**

Wazee Digital considers protection of your personal information a high priority, and therefore, Wazee Digital uses SSL encryption technologies to insure privacy when transmitting sensitive information to our servers. Unfortunately, there is no perfect security on the Internet, and Wazee Digital does not guarantee that our Website is impenetrable or invulnerable to hackers or other security breaches. Our corporate values, ethical standards, policies and practices are committed to the protection of user information. Upon request we offer visitors the ability to have inaccuracies corrected in contact information and communications that the user/visitor has directed to our Website. Users can have this information corrected by sending us an email at [legal@wazeedigital.com](mailto:legal@wazeedigital.com). 

**About Cookies**

When you visit the Wazee Digital Website, we place a text file called a “cookie” in the browser directory of your computer’s hard drive. A cookie is a small piece of information that a website can store on your web browser and later retrieve. Cookies contain non-personally identifiable information about the user and only identify the user’s computer. You can set your browser’s options not to accept cookies, but this may prevent you from accessing all of the features of the Wazee Digital. 

Cookies enable the Website to recognize the information you have consented to give us and help us determine what portions of the Website are most appropriate for your professional needs. As a result, cookies shall allow you to access your clip bins and order archive and edit your Registration Data. Your Internet browser software probably enables you to refuse any cookies placed on your hard drive. If you choose to refuse cookies placed by our Website, you will have to log into the Website with your user name and password. 

Wazee Digital uses clear GIFs, a tiny 1×1 pixel GIF, to digitally watermark our images, in both a visible and invisible manner. When you purchase a licensed image from Wazee Digital, the visible watermark is then removed from the image, however, in certain lower resolution images, an invisible watermark may remain, allowing Wazee Digital and the third party to track certain usage of such images on the Internet. 

We use “pixel tags” (also called “web beacons” or “clear gifs”), which are tiny graphic images, on our Website and in our emails. Pixel tags help us analyze our customers’ online behavior and measure the effectiveness of our Website and our advertising. We work with service providers that help us track, collect, and analyze this information. 

Pixel tags on our Website may be used to collect information about your visit, including the pages you view, the features you use, the links you click, and other actions you take in connection with our Website. This information may include your computer’s Internet protocol (IP) address, your browser type, your operating system, date and time information, and other technical information about your computer. We may also track certain information about the identity of the website you visited immediately before coming to our Website. We do not otherwise track any information about your use of other websites. 

Pixel tags and cookies in our emails may be used to track your interactions with those messages, such as when you receive, open, or click a link in an email message from us. We also work with third-party companies, including Google, that use tracking technologies to serve advertisements on our behalf across the Internet. These companies may collect information about your visits to our Website and your interaction with our advertising and other communications. If you would like more information about this practice or to opt out of having your information used by these companies, please visit<http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp> or <http://www.google.com/privacy/ads/>. 

We may combine the information we collect through cookies and pixel tags with other information we have collected from you. This information may be used to improve our Website, to personalize your online experience, to tailor our communications with you, to determine the effectiveness of our advertising, and for other internal business purposes. 

If at any time you believe that Wazee Digital has not followed the above policy, or if you would like your information to be removed from our system, please e-mail us at [sales@wazeedigital.com](mailto:sales@wazeedigital.com). 

**Age Restriction**

The Wazee Digital Website and the content therein are intended for use by persons age 18 and older. Anyone under the age of 18 should **_not_** establish an account with Wazee Digital and should **_not_** provide any personal information to Wazee Digital. 

**What About Other Websites Linked to Our Website**

We are not responsible for the practices employed by sites liked to or from our website or the information or content contained therein. Often links to other sites are provided solely as pointers to information on topics that may be useful to the users of our website. We do not endorse, approve, certify or control these sites and we do not guarantee the accuracy of the information presented on any third party site. Please remember that when you use a link to go from our website to another site, our Privacy Policy is no longer in effect. Your browsing and interaction on any other site, including sites which have a link on our website, is subject to that site’s own rules and policies. Please read over those rules and policies before proceeding. 

**Changes to policy**

We reserve the right to change the terms of this privacy policy at any time. When we make changes, we will revise the “last updated” date at the top of the policy. If there are material changes to this statement or in how Wazee Digital will use your personal information, we will notify you by prominently posting a notice of such changes here or on our home page, or by sending you an email. We encourage you to review this policy whenever you visit our website.
